thisiscentralstation.com 2011-11-24

# Central Station, Your Privacy

### Privacy Statement

**17 September 2009**

**Introduction**

This privacy statement sets out our policy with respect to the privacy of visitors to our website and the manner in which we collect, store and use personal information derived from our visitors.

We have adopted this policy voluntarily and may update the policy from time to time.

**Which Websites does this Policy apply to?**

**This policy applies to the website www.thisiscentralstation.com ("the Website"):**

This policy does not apply to information obtained other than through the Website.

**What Personal Information is collected by us?**

**We collect information which is volunteered by you.  Sometimes this information is necessary to operate certain aspects of our website (eg. where you have requested updates via email, we would require your email address).  Other information may be requested to improve the website and/or the services we offer from the Website.**

The information may be requested at various stages of your visiting the Website, be it registration as a member or use of forums and message boards.  In all cases, the type of information requested will be clear to you.

**How we will use Personal Information collected at the Websites**

Demographic information (i.e. information relating to age, gender, location etc. but not specifically identifying you) may be aggregated and disclosed to third parties.  This information will never identify you or your computer personally.

We may use your personal information to update you on the services and features that we provide from the Website, unless you have specifically opted out of this feature through the opt out procedures. If you request the updates from us, it is necessary for us to hold the personal information you provide.

We will not sell or disclose your personal information to third parties other than our processors without your prior consent.

**Cookies**

**A cookie is a small information file that is saved to your computer's hard disk to store information about yourself so that when you visit the website subsequently you do not have to enter that information again.  The Website makes use of cookies for this purpose.**

In addition, we may store on our servers your IP address so that we can identify returning visitors to our site.

**Management of your Personal Information**

If you are registered visitor, you will be entitled to update and/or remove your personal information from our database by following the procedure laid out at the Website

**Security**

We will use all reasonable measures to ensure the security of your personal information held by us.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may from time to time update this privacy statement.  You may determine the latest update by reference to the date at the top of this statement.  Any significant departures from this privacy statement will be notified to you, provided that we have your email address.

**Children under 16**

We will not hold personal information where the subject has disclosed that it is under the age of 16 unless we have also received permission of a parent or guardian.

**Other websites**

This privacy statement does not cover the links within this site to other websites.  We therefore encourage you to read the privacy statements of the other websites.

**Comments and Suggestions**

We are committed to developing a practical and user-friendly privacy policy.  If you have any comments or suggestions regarding this, please send them to:
